MALATI SAIDAVA

+91 76216 52423 malatiaidava@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/malatisaidava malati.saidava.com Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

A self-learner to research more into technical field for enhancement of conventional methods in rural development project, a explorer to get an opportunity where I can apply my skills, knowledge and expertise to achieve Sustainable Development Goals.

SKILLS

Technicals Skills

- Fusion 360
- HTML
- Basic Electronics
- Arduino
- Web development
- Teaching
- 3D Printing
- Laser Cutting

Personal Skills

- Communication skills
- Interpersonal skills
- Management skills
- Self Learner

EDUCATION

Master in Social Work

October 2019- June 2021 MIPLVP, Gujarat, India

Msc Information Technology

December 2015 - March 2017 S J Varmora College,Surendranagar

Bachelor in Computer Application

January 2013 - April 2015 S J Varmora College, Surendranagar, Gujarat, India

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

EnCube Labs India Pvt. Ltd. Mentors

Dec 2017 - Feb 2018

- Conducting Making events for schools in multiple cities in India.
- Making Art Models for Showcase
- Managing Atal Tinkering Lab
- Making Electronic Circuits
- Creating Gujarati Content for Tutorials
- Conducting Web Development Session
- Conducting Art Session String Art, Marble Art
- Teaching Various Robot Assembly

The Good Human Being Foundation IT Support Mar 2018 – Oct 2019

- Training college students for digital fabrication skills
- Research and Survey for technical interventions
- Conducting Workshops on Arduino
- Teaching Robotics to Girls
- Website & Server Management
- Documentation and Media content management
- Video Making and Presentation Design

Prayatna Charitable Trust Trainer

May 2021 - Current

- Training students online for web development.
- Project Handling of 21st Century Skills
- Leading School Clubs for Tinkering India Initiative

Volunteer Experience

Maker Yatra 2018

Visiting Villages to meet innovator and entrepreneurs and connecting them to young students and other yatri participated in program.

Web Design www.tghbf.org/makeryatra

Rural Makerfest 2018

A showcase conducted at Idar for Schools and parents to share and show innovation and STEM models .

Further Interest

- Working for STEM Education
- Develop skills for girls to learn technology
- Women Empowerment
- Rural Development